meigeeteam.com 2019-01-06

# Privacy Policy

We respect your right to privacy. This policy summarises what personally identifiable information we may collect, and how we can use this information. This policy also describes other important topics concerning your privacy.

**Information Collection**

When you visit meigeeteam.com, we collect your IP address and web browser information. If you want to create an account at meigeetem.com, we require you provide your personal information: name, address and email address. When you purchase extensions from meigeetem.com, you may need to provide us some more additional information: address, phone, company.

If you use a credit card to purchase products from our site, your name on the credit card, the credit card number, expiration date and billing address will be encrypted as it passes over the Internet. meigeeteam.com does not keep your credit card information for online credit-card transactions, but such information is simply passed through our contracted payment processing vendor.

**Use of Information**

Names and email addresses and other information which collected from customers at the time of a sale in order to complete the purchase. We do not share the information with third parties. We are firmly against spam and neither participate nor promote any activities that assist spammers.

**How we protect and store personal information**

We commit to protect personal information. We store your information on our secured server. We use SSL for the checkout process which help you keep your billing information safe. No credit card information is saved on our system. We don’t share your personal information with any other third parties. Unfortunately, there is no 100% safe way of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage. So we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Meigeeteam.com reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of our websites after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.
